<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeremy Hintz</title>
    <description>Portfolio site, blog, and random stuff from Jeremy Hintz</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 22:58:31 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 22:58:31 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Example Post</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;an-h1-header&quot;&gt;An h1 header&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique&lt;/strong&gt; senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. &lt;em&gt;Aenean ultricies mi vitae est&lt;/em&gt;. Mauris placerat eleifend leo. Quisque sit amet est et sapien ullamcorper pharetra. Vestibulum erat wisi, condimentum sed, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;commodo vitae&lt;/code&gt;, ornare sit amet, wisi. Aenean fermentum, elit eget tincidunt condimentum, eros ipsum  rutrum orci, sagittis tempus lacus enim ac dui. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Donec non enim&lt;/a&gt; in turpis pulvinar facilisis. Ut felis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;this bullet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;that bullet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;the other bullet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Block quotes are
written like so.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;They can span multiple paragraphs,
if you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-h2-header&quot;&gt;An h2 header&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a numbered list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;first item&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;second item&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;third item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;!-- OR --&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-python&quot; data-lang=&quot;python&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kn&quot;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;time&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Quick, count to ten!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;tick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;for&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ow&quot;&gt;in&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;range&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;):&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# (but not *too* quick)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;sleep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;0.5&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-h3-header&quot;&gt;An h3 header&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now a nested list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;First, get these ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;carrots&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;celery&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;lentils&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Boil some water.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dump everything in the pot and follow
this algorithm:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find wooden spoon
uncover pot
stir
cover pot
balance wooden spoon precariously on pot handle
wait 10 minutes
goto first step (or shut off burner when done)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Do not bump wooden spoon or it will fall.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notice again how text always lines up on 4-space indents (including
that last line which continues item 3 above).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a link to &lt;a href=&quot;http://foo.bar&quot;&gt;a website&lt;/a&gt;, to a &lt;a href=&quot;/feed.xml&quot;&gt;local
doc&lt;/a&gt;, and to a &lt;a href=&quot;#an-h2-header&quot;&gt;section heading in the current
doc&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s a footnote &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tables can look like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;size&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;material&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;color&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;leather&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;brown&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;hemp canvas&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;natural&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;glass&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;transparent&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Table: Shoes, their sizes, and what they’re made of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(The above is the caption for the table.)
A horizontal rule follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a definition list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;apples&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Good for making applesauce.&lt;/dd&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;oranges&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Citrus!&lt;/dd&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;tomatoes&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;There’s no “e” in tomatoe.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, text is indented 4 spaces. (Put a blank line between each
term/definition pair to spread things out more.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a “line block”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Line one&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Line too&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Line tree&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and images can be specified like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;image fit&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pic01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beautiful Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And note that you can backslash-escape any punctuation characters
which you wish to be displayed literally, ex.: `foo`, *bar*, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Footnote text goes here. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/typography/dummy-text/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/typography/dummy-text/</guid>
        
        <category>dummy text</category>
        
        <category>random</category>
        
        <category>type</category>
        
        
        <category>typography</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man must explore, and this is exploration at its greatest</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The quick, brown fox jumps over a lazy dog. DJs flock by when MTV ax quiz prog. Junk MTV quiz graced by fox whelps. Bawds jog, flick quartz, vex nymphs. Waltz, bad nymph, for quick jigs vex! Fox nymphs grab quick-jived waltz. Brick quiz whangs jumpy veldt fox. Bright vixens jump; dozy fowl quack. Quick wafting zephyrs vex bold Jim. Quick zephyrs blow, vexing daft Jim. Sex-charged fop blew my junk TV quiz. How quickly daft jumping zebras vex. Two driven jocks help fax my big quiz. Quick, Baz, get my woven flax jodhpurs! “Now fax quiz Jack! “ my brave ghost pled. Five quacking zephyrs jolt my wax bed. Flummoxed by job, kvetching W. zaps Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cozy sphinx waves quart jug of bad milk. A very bad quack might jinx zippy fowls. Few quips galvanized the mock jury box. Quick brown dogs jump over the lazy fox. The jay, pig, fox, zebra, and my wolves quack! Blowzy red vixens fight for a quick jump. Joaquin Phoenix was gazed by MTV for luck. A wizard’s job is to vex chumps quickly in fog. Watch “Jeopardy! “, Alex Trebek’s fun TV quiz game. Woven silk pyjamas exchanged for blue quartz. Brawny gods just flocked up to quiz and vex him. Adjusting quiver and bow, Zompyc[1] killed the fox. My faxed joke won a pager in the cable TV quiz show. Amazingly few discotheques provide jukeboxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My girl wove six dozen plaid jackets before she quit. Six big devils from Japan quickly forgot how to waltz. Big July earthquakes confound zany experimental vow. Foxy parsons quiz and cajole the lovably dim wiki-girl. Have a pick: twenty six letters - no forcing a jumbled quiz! Crazy Fredericka bought many very exquisite opal jewels. Sixty zippers were quickly picked from the woven jute bag. A quick movement of the enemy will jeopardize six gunboats. All questions asked by five watch experts amazed the judge. Jack quietly moved up front and seized the big ball of wax. The quick, brown fox jumps over a lazy dog. DJs flock by when MTV ax quiz prog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Junk MTV quiz graced by fox whelps. Bawds jog, flick quartz, vex nymphs. Waltz, bad nymph, for quick jigs vex! Fox nymphs grab quick-jived waltz. Brick quiz whangs jumpy veldt fox. Bright vixens jump; dozy fowl quack. Quick wafting zephyrs vex bold Jim. Quick zephyrs blow, vexing daft Jim. Sex-charged fop blew my junk TV quiz. How quickly daft jumping zebras vex. Two driven jocks help fax my big quiz. Quick, Baz, get my woven flax jodhpurs! “Now fax quiz Jack! “ my brave ghost pled. Five quacking zephyrs jolt my wax bed. Flummoxed by job, kvetching W. zaps Iraq. Cozy sphinx waves quart jug of bad milk. A very bad quack might jinx zippy fowls. Few quips galvanized the mock jury box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quick brown dogs jump over the lazy fox. The jay, pig, fox, zebra, and my wolves quack! Blowzy red vixens fight for a quick jump. Joaquin Phoenix was gazed by MTV for luck. A wizard’s job is to vex chumps quickly in fog. Watch “Jeopardy! “, Alex Trebek’s fun TV quiz game. Woven silk pyjamas exchanged for blue quartz. Brawny gods just flocked up to quiz and vex him. Adjusting quiver and bow, Zompyc[1] killed the fox. My faxed joke won a pager in the cable TV quiz show. Amazingly few discotheques provide jukeboxes. My girl wove six dozen plaid jackets before she quit. Six big devils from Japan quickly forgot how to waltz. Big July earthquakes confound zany experimental vow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foxy parsons quiz and cajole the lovably dim wiki-girl. Have a pick: twenty six letters - no forcing a jumbled quiz! Crazy Fredericka bought many very exquisite opal jewels. Sixty zippers were quickly picked from the woven jute bag. A quick movement of the enemy will jeopardize six gunboats. All questions asked by five watch experts amazed the judge. Jack quietly moved up front and seized the big ball of wax. The quick, brown fox jumps over a lazy dog. DJs flock by when MTV ax quiz prog. Junk MTV quiz graced by fox whelps. Bawds jog, flick quartz, vex nymphs. Waltz, bad nymph, for quick jigs vex! Fox nymphs grab quick-jived waltz. Brick quiz whangs jumpy veldt fox. Bright vixens jump; dozy fowl quack. Quick wafting zephyrs vex bold Jim. Quick zephyrs blow, vexing daft Jim. Sex-charged fop blew my junk TV quiz. How quickly daft jumping zebras vex. Two driven jocks help fax my big quiz. Quick, Baz, get my woven flax jodhpurs! “Now fax quiz Jack! “ my brave ghost pled. Five quacking zephyrs jolt my wax bed. Flummoxed by job, kvetching W. zaps Iraq. Cozy sphinx waves quart jug of bad milk. A very bad quack might jinx zippy fowls. Few quips galvanized the mock jury box. Quick brown dogs jump over the lazy fox. The jay, pig, fox, zebr&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/misc/man-must-explore/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/misc/man-must-explore/</guid>
        
        <category>random</category>
        
        <category>type</category>
        
        
        <category>misc</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinosaurs are extinct today</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One morning, when Gregor Samsa woke from troubled dreams, he found himself transformed in his bed into a horrible vermin. He lay on his armour-like back, and if he lifted his head a little he could see his brown belly, slightly domed and divided by arches into stiff sections. The bedding was hardly able to cover it and seemed ready to slide off any moment. His many legs, pitifully thin compared with the size of the rest of him, waved about helplessly as he looked. “What’s happened to me? “ he thought. It wasn’t a dream. His room, a proper human room although a little too small, lay peacefully between its four familiar walls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A collection of textile samples lay spread out on the table - Samsa was a travelling salesman - and above it there hung a picture that he had recently cut out of an illustrated magazine and housed in a nice, gilded frame. It showed a lady fitted out with a fur hat and fur boa who sat upright, raising a heavy fur muff that covered the whole of her lower arm towards the viewer. Gregor then turned to look out the window at the dull weather. Drops of rain could be heard hitting the pane, which made him feel quite sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How about if I sleep a little bit longer and forget all this nonsense”, he thought, but that was something he was unable to do because he was used to sleeping on his right, and in his present state couldn’t get into that position. However hard he threw himself onto his right, he always rolled back to where he was. He must have tried it a hundred times, shut his eyes so that he wouldn’t have to look at the floundering legs, and only stopped when he began to feel a mild, dull pain there that he had never felt before. “Oh, God”, he thought, “what a strenuous career it is that I’ve chosen! Travelling day in and day out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing business like this takes much more effort than doing your own business at home, and on top of that there’s the curse of travelling, worries about making train connections, bad and irregular food, contact with different people all the time so that you can never get to know anyone or become friendly with them. It can all go to Hell! “ He felt a slight itch up on his belly; pushed himself slowly up on his back towards the headboard so that he could lift his head better; found where the itch was, and saw that it was covered with lots of little white spots which he didn’t know what to make of; and when he tried to feel the place with one of his legs he drew it quickly back because as soon as he touched it he was overcome by a cold shudder. He slid back into his former position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Getting up early all the time”, he thought, “it makes you stupid. You’ve got to get enough sleep. Other travelling salesmen live a life of luxury. For instance, whenever I go back to the guest house during the morning to copy out the contract, these gentlemen are always still sitting there eating their breakfasts. I ought to just try that with my boss; I’d get kicked out on the spot. But who knows, maybe that would be the best thing for me. If I didn’t have my parents to think about I’d have given in my notice a long time ago, I’d have gone up to the boss and told him just what I think, tell him everything I would, let him know just what I feel. He’d fall right off his desk!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it’s a funny sort of business to be sitting up there at your desk, talking down at your subordinates from up there, especially when you have to go right up close because the boss is hard of hearing. Well, there’s still some hope; once I’ve got the money together to pay off my parents’ debt to him - another five or six years I suppose - that’s definitely what I’ll do. That’s when I’ll make the big change. First of all though, I’ve got to get up, my train leaves at five. “ And he looked over at the alarm clock, ticking on the chest of drawers. “God in Heaven! “ he thought. It was half past six and the hands were quietly moving forwards, it was even later than half past, more like quarter to seven. Had the alarm clock not rung? He could see from the bed that it had been set for four o’clock as it should have been; it certainly must have rung. Yes, but was it possible to quietly sleep through that furniture-rattling noise? True, he had not slept peacefully, but probably all the more deeply because of that. What should he do now? The next train went at seven; if he were to catch that he would have to rush like mad and the collection of samples was still not packed, and he did not at all feel particularly fresh and lively. And even if he did catch the train he would not avoid his boss’s anger.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bookshelf/dinosaurs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bookshelf/dinosaurs/</guid>
        
        <category>extinction</category>
        
        
        <category>bookshelf</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
